[{"answer": " Hi, Tony", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Hi, Ms. Smith", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hi, Tony", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " How was your week at school", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Hi, Ms. Smith", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " It was okay", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": " How was your week at school", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " How did your geometry test go", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 16, "question": " It was okay", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Im not sure.  It was pretty hard", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 17, "question": " How did your geometry test go", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Well, we did a lot of prep for it and you knew all the information, so Im sur", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Im not sure.  It was pretty hard", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " I hope so.  The studying helped, but I guess Ill see what happened next wee", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, we did a lot of prep for it and you knew all the information, so Im sur", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Good.  So, was anything giving you difficulties at school this week", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I hope so.  The studying helped, but I guess Ill see what happened next wee", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Yeah, my History class was kind of confusing", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Good.  So, was anything giving you difficulties at school this week", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " What were you studying this week", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Yeah, my History class was kind of confusing", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " The Civil Rights Movement.  We were learning about Martin Luther King, Jr", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 32, "question": " What were you studying this week", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " OK.  So, what was difficult about the lesson", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 33, "question": " The Civil Rights Movement.  We were learning about Martin Luther King, Jr", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I was having a hard time tuning in to the teacher.  Shes kind of boring and ", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": " OK.  So, what was difficult about the lesson", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " All right.  Why dont we review a little bit about Martin Luther King, Jr?  Ca", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I was having a hard time tuning in to the teacher.  Shes kind of boring and ", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Well, he was a guy who was trying to change things in the United States.  T", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 42, "question": " All right.  Why dont we review a little bit about Martin Luther King, Jr?  Ca", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Thats right.  He was a civil rights leader in the U.S.  Now, do you remembe", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well, he was a guy who was trying to change things in the United States.  T", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Sorry, I dont remember", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Thats right.  He was a civil rights leader in the U.S.  Now, do you remembe", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Thats OK.  King believed in non-violence.  So, he never used violence as ", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Sorry, I dont remember", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I kind of remember that", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Thats OK.  King believed in non-violence.  So, he never used violence as ", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Good.  Youre remembering a lot so far.  Can you think of any of the thing", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I kind of remember that", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Umm, I remember that he was mad about the rule that African Americans had t", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Good.  Youre remembering a lot so far.  Can you think of any of the thing", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Thats right.  They boycotted the buses in Montgomery, Alabama.  Can yo", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Umm, I remember that he was mad about the rule that African Americans had t", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Lets see I think he went on a long walk with a bunch of people, and the", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Thats right.  They boycotted the buses in Montgomery, Alabama.  Can yo", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Good.  Thats right.  He led a march from Selma to Montgomery, Alabam", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Lets see I think he went on a long walk with a bunch of people, and the", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " He won the Nobel Peace Prize", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Good.  Thats right.  He led a march from Selma to Montgomery, Alabam", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thats true, but not many people know that.  What do most people kno", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 81, "question": " He won the Nobel Peace Prize", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Oh, I remember.  He gave the famous I Have a Dream speech", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thats true, but not many people know that.  What do most people kno", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " You got it.  That speech, which he gave in Washington D.C., is very famous", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Oh, I remember.  He gave the famous I Have a Dream speech", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yes, Ive heard it many times in school", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 90, "question": " You got it.  That speech, which he gave in Washington D.C., is very famous", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " So, do you think King was an important person in U.S. history", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Yes, Ive heard it many times in school", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Yes", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 92, "question": " So, do you think King was an important person in U.S. history", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Yes", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Because he helped a lot to get equal rights for everyone living in the U.S., n", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Good answer.  And does Martin Luther King, Jr. still help people today", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Because he helped a lot to get equal rights for everyone living in the U.S., n", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " No, he was assassinated", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Good answer.  And does Martin Luther King, Jr. still help people today", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Yes, unfortunately that is true. He was killed in 1968.  So, it seems like yo", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 100, "question": " No, he was assassinated", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "09-09", "aSentId": 103, "question": " Yes, unfortunately that is true. He was killed in 1968.  So, it seems like yo", "qSentId": 102}]
